Nathan (SB) Jang

Software Engineer

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with a background in the fine dining culinary scene for over 8 years. My strong passion and creativity towards Culinary Arts easily transformed into building software products. I found a similar connection in the level of focus in perfecting a dish to finding a path to solve problems.

PROJECTS

KUSAKABE (github) — React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose

Make an online order MERN stack app for famous Omakase restaurant named 'KUSAKABE' using React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Material UI

Calculator (github) — React, Codesandbox

During the React hackathon, built a simple calculator with other developers using React and Codesandbox

Nathan's recipe blog (github) — MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth, Material Design

Make recipe sites from my experience using MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth and Material design for styling

Minesweeper (github) — HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Simple Minesweeper Game using HTML, CSS, Java Script

EXPERIENCE

The Shota, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

MAR 2019 - MAR 2020

Trained and supervised new staff members. Took charge of kitchen team activities to assure accurate food preparation, attractive plating, and timely delivery with precise food temperature.

Kusakabe, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

OCT 2016 - MAR 2019

Served as a sushi & kitchen chef in an Omakase(Chef's Choice Prix Fixe Menu) restaurant serving Sushi-in-Kaiseki style. Served from 2 up to 6 customers at a bar setting. Assisted Kaiseki chef to successfully execute the entire course meals.

Walnut Creek, CA 94597 (415) 317-5944 sbtan1989@gmail.com https://grey1287.github.io/Portfolio/ linkedin.com/in/nathan-sb-j github.com/grey1287

SKILLS

Languages

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python

Databases and Frameworks

React | Express | MongoDB | Mongoose | Material design

Tools

Figma, Trello

EDUCATION

General Assembly

Software Engineering Immersive San Francisco, CA

12 weeks of full-time coding bootcamp in Software Engineering program running from October 2020 to February 2021

California Culinary Academy

Culinary ArtsSan Francisco, CA

LANGUAGES

English, Korean